<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Community calls on InterMine - data integration, analysis, and warehousing</title>
    <link>http://intermine.org/community-calls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community calls on InterMine - data integration, analysis, and warehousing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://intermine.org/community-calls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Outreach Calls</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/community-calls/outreach-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/community-calls/outreach-calls/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re an organisation that runs an InterMine, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance you have (or wish to have!) a community around you that may need engagement, training, support, and encouragement to join in. We run quarterly Community Outreach calls, where we talk about different ways to run a successful, happy community.
The call info (2019, 2018) is always posted on GitHub so others can comment openly and add suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer calls</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/community-calls/developer-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/community-calls/developer-calls/</guid>
      <description>InterMine developer calls are held roughly once a month, on the first tuesday of the month, generally at 17:00 UK time (with occasional time shifts around daylight savings clock changes). These calls are generally techie-oriented and consist of topics such as:
 Upcoming technical updates to InterMine. Discussions regarding the InterMine data model. General updates, e.g. upcoming training events, Google Summer of Code, conferences.  The call is open to anyone, but developers and InterMine admins are especially encouraged to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>