<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>InterMine - data integration, analysis, and warehousing</title>
    <link>http://intermine.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on InterMine - data integration, analysis, and warehousing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://intermine.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/team/gos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/team/gos/</guid>
      <description>InterMine is part of the Micklem Lab, led by Gos Micklem. Gos is also director of the Cambridge Computational Biology Institute. Gos can often be found writing grants and winning Department of Genetics awards for enthusiastic lecturing. (He says that this was probably a statistical anomaly).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning about InterMine</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/contributing/learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/contributing/learning/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! We&amp;rsquo;re excited to have you join the community. InterMine integrates biological data, but you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a biologist to contribute to InterMine. Some of our entry-level issues only require knowledge of the relevant programming language, but others may require more in-depth understanding.
If you&amp;rsquo;d like to learn a bit more about InterMine, we have a nice 5 minute video for you to sum things up:
 If you prefer textual learning resources, you could look at the InterMine documentation for a technical overview of InterMine&amp;rsquo;s server, the FlyMine tutorials for a biologist/bioinformatician oriented overview, or you could hop straight into our Python tutorials to learn more about querying our data model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New to open source?</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/contributing/new-to-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/contributing/new-to-open-source/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve never made a pull request before, or you&amp;rsquo;ve used git a little but never collaboratively? Have a look through the open source guide to submitting contributions to give you a good idea of how things work.
Some of our issues are marked first-timers-only - these are issues that may be relatively straightforward, where we&amp;rsquo;ll happily walk you through steps you&amp;rsquo;re unsure about. (psst, you can also search GitHub for all issues marked with this label, not just InterMine).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Previous InterMine Members</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/contributors/previousinterminers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/contributors/previousinterminers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing - tickets to try</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/contributing/tickets-to-try/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/contributing/tickets-to-try/</guid>
      <description> Interested in helping out? Here are some of the issues we&amp;rsquo;re looking for help with. Please read our contributing guidelines first!.
  OpenTagGrabber.init(&#34;intermineIssues&#34;,&#34;http://tag-grabber.apps.intermine.org/issues&#34;);  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSOC 2019</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/contributors/gsoc2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/contributors/gsoc2019/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSOC 2018</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/contributors/gsoc2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/contributors/gsoc2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSOC 2017</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/contributors/gsoc2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/contributors/gsoc2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/team/adrian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/team/adrian/</guid>
      <description>Computer Scientist with a M.Sc. in Data Science &amp; Machine Learning. His interests span from Machine Learning applied to cancer bioinformatics to the handling of biomedical big data.
Previously, Adrián has worked in a variety of places in both the private and public sectors, such as the Spanish National Supercomputing Center and the Spanish Council for Scientific Research. He also has participated as Google Summer of Code student with InterMine in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/team/daniela/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/team/daniela/</guid>
      <description>Software Engineer with 15+ years of experience in web applications development in a variety of industries. Experienced in J2EE open source frameworks, servers, libraries and web services.
She joined the InterMine team in 2010, working for 3 years, primarily in the backend development, then she moved away to the game industry but she changed ideas very soon and came back thinking that genes and proteins are more fun than treasures and crowns!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/team/herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/team/herald/</guid>
      <description>A passionate programmer who ended up at Intermine by chance following his interest in Clojure(Script). Is mostly versed in frontend development, but doesn&#39;t mind as long as he gets to write code in a fun language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/team/rachel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/team/rachel/</guid>
      <description>Biologist/bioinformatician with over 10 years experience working with InterMine and complex biological data, she forms the liaison between the biology and the software development. Rachel also runs training workshops for InterMine users and provides help-desk support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/team/sergio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/team/sergio/</guid>
      <description>With InterMine since 2007, has worked mostly in the production of modMine (modENCODE project) and ThaleMine (Araport project). Likes databases and data visualization, has produced a music album of his compositions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/team/yo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/team/yo/</guid>
      <description>GSoC Organisation Admin, software engineer with a focus on front-end technologies such as Javascript, ClojureScript, and User Interfaces. May be spotted blogging, tweeting from her own account, @intermineorg, @gmodproject, or updating the InterMine homepage. Loves interacting with open source communities. She&#39;s also a Software Sustainability Institute Fellow, and is studying effects of community and usability on open source projects for an EngD with the University of Manchester. In her spare time you can find her running, cycling, or reading speculative fiction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Clients</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/developers/apiclients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/developers/apiclients/</guid>
      <description>We have client libraries to make querying InterMine super-easy! There&amp;rsquo;s one for each of R, Python, Perl, JavaScript (node or browser), Ruby, and Java</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Documentation</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/developers/apidocumentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/developers/apidocumentation/</guid>
      <description>Dive straight into our API with interactive live documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>InterMine Code of Conduct Like the technical community as a whole, the InterMine team and community is made up of a mixture of professionals and volunteers from all over the world, working on every aspect of the mission - including mentorship, teaching, and connecting people.
Diversity is one of our huge strengths, but it can also lead to communication issues and unhappiness. To that end, we have a few ground rules that we ask people to adhere to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Outreach Calls</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/community-calls/outreach-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/community-calls/outreach-calls/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re an organisation that runs an InterMine, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance you have (or wish to have!) a community around you that may need engagement, training, support, and encouragement to join in. We run quarterly Community Outreach calls, where we talk about different ways to run a successful, happy community.
The call info (2019, 2018) is always posted on GitHub so others can comment openly and add suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing Guidelines</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/contributing/guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/contributing/guidelines/</guid>
      <description>InterMine has a large variety of repositories in a number of different languages. We have a list of issues marked up with labels such as &amp;ldquo;Help Wanted&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Beginner&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Good first bug&amp;rdquo; that you can choose from, but you&amp;rsquo;re welcome to offer help on any issue if you think you understand what&amp;rsquo;s going on and what needs to be done.
Picking up tasks If you find an issue that interests you, here&amp;rsquo;s what to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing to InterMine</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/developers/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/developers/contributing/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;d like to start contributing to InterMine, whether you&amp;rsquo;re a student interested in GSoC, a developer from a lab running InterMine, a Hacktoberfest enthusiast, or something else - here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to know!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer calls</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/community-calls/developer-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/community-calls/developer-calls/</guid>
      <description>InterMine developer calls are held roughly once a month, on the first tuesday of the month, generally at 17:00 UK time (with occasional time shifts around daylight savings clock changes). These calls are generally techie-oriented and consist of topics such as:
 Upcoming technical updates to InterMine. Discussions regarding the InterMine data model. General updates, e.g. upcoming training events, Google Summer of Code, conferences.  The call is open to anyone, but developers and InterMine admins are especially encouraged to attend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer docs</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/developers/developerdocs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/developers/developerdocs/</guid>
      <description>Documentation for new and veteran InterMine developers. Includes getting started tutorials, system requirements, configuration info, and troubleshooting tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer email list</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/developers/developeremaillist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/developers/developeremaillist/</guid>
      <description>Sign up, ask for help, get updates, or just browse the archives to see if a problem you&amp;rsquo;re having has happened before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISA-InterMine: accelerating and rewarding data sharing</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/projects/isa-intermine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/projects/isa-intermine/</guid>
      <description>The ISA-InterMine grant is funded by the Wellcome Trust, collaborating with ISATools in Oxford to integrate ISA metadata into InterMine and make creating InterMine instances quickly and easily on the cloud. Read more details in our announcment blog post. This grant&amp;rsquo;s start date is April 2018 and it runs for three years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InterMine Android and iOS Apps</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/mobile-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/mobile-apps/</guid>
      <description>InterMine&#39;s mobile apps allow you to carry the power of multiple InterMines in your pocket. They include a cross-InterMine search tool, as well as alowing you to browse lists, templates, and to create a selection of &#34;favourites&#34; - perhaps a set of publications to review or a collection of interesting genes.
Android  Search genes across multiple InterMines, as well as viewing lists, templates, and creating favourites. Developed by Daria Komkova.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InterMine Chat (Discord)</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/developers/supportchat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/developers/supportchat/</guid>
      <description>Chat in real time with InterMiners (UK day time) or with the rest of the community. There&amp;rsquo;s a general chit-chat channel for important stuff like cat pictures, and a support channel for technical queries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InterMine Community Contributors</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/contributors/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/contributors/community/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InterMine Registry</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/developers/registry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/developers/registry/</guid>
      <description>Need a list of InterMines programmatically? Our Registry Swagger API gives you interactive API documentation, or you can browse a list of InterMines if you prefer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InterMine on GitHub</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/developers/github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/developers/github/</guid>
      <description>This is where the code lives! Feel free to fork, star, make issues and bug reports, or even make a pull request if you have a fix or feature for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making data FAIR using InterMine</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/projects/fair-bbsrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/projects/fair-bbsrc/</guid>
      <description>This grant is funded by the BBSRC, and runs for three years starting July 2017, with a focus on making InterMine and its data more FAIR - that is, Findable, Accessible, Interoperable, and Reusable. Read more in our grant launch blog post</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Credits</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/credits/</guid>
      <description>InterMine Homepage Copyright InterMine 2017-2019 Site This site is generated using the static site generator hugo and hosted on GitHub pages.
Icons SVG icons used on the site are courtesy of IcoMoon and academicons (pubmed icon). Organism icons on the home page are made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com.
Contributors and Team See contributors and team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials and videos</title>
      <link>http://intermine.org/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://intermine.org/tutorials/</guid>
      <description>Training workshops and Exercises We typically carry out a few training workshops each year - keep your eye on our calendar or [twitter feed]https://twitter.com/intermineorg) to find out when registration is open. The materials are available online and designed to be worked through in a self-led or tutor-led manner. These include:
 Intro to data analysis with the InterMine user interface 🐍 Data analysis workflows in Python  Python Pax6 Workflow (unsolved):  Python Pax6 Workflow (with answers):   🇷 Data analysis workflows in R  R Pax6 Workflow (unsolved)  R Pax6 Workflow (with answers)   🇷 Advanced exercises: producing figures and data visualisations in R  Enrichment and visualisations (unsolved):  Enrichment and visualisations (with answers):    Videos Here&amp;rsquo;s a short list of video tutorials produced by community members.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>